

Yahya El Kajouai El Bannasri

Software Engineer

💌 yahyakajouai@gmail.com 📞 +34 611 452 812 👂 Barcelona, Spain

30/04/1998 in https://www.linkedin.com/in/yahyaelk/

Profile

Software engineer with +4 years of experience in development, testing and maintenance of software systems. Domain of several platforms, languages and integrated systems. Experience in the latest development tools and procedures. Capable of effective self-management in independent projects. Good collaboration skills within a productive team.

Professional Experience

Software Engineer

Bridgestone Mobility Solutions

11/2021 – present Barcelona, Spain

- Led the development of a new product features that was successfully launched to
- Developed a Java Spring Boot microservice that integrated with an existing React.js front-end.
- Maintained and improved software components written in Java and JavaScript that were integral to the functioning of the company's website.
- Used Java 11 features to improve code readability and performance.
- Wrote and automated tests for new software features, ensuring more than 80% code coverage.

Full Stack Developer

Indra

04/2019 – 11/2021 Barcelona, Spain

- Contributed to development of front-end user interface using ReactJS, created reusable components, implemented Redux to manage state.
- Developed RESTful services using Java Spring Boot framework and integrated with MySQL database.
- Successfully implemented features such as registration, login, account overview and transactions.
- Developed comprehensive unit and integration tests to ensure the quality of the codebase and reduce bugs.

Education

Web Applications Development

Institut Pedralbes

09/2019 – 06/2020 Barcelona, Spain

Mobile and Desktop Applications Development

Institut Pedralbes

09/2017 – 06/2019 Barcelona, Spain

Languages

• Spanish

English

Arabic

Catalan

Skills

React.js Spring Framework

Java Script

Oracle Database MySQL Database

Spring Boot Apache Kafka

GIT Jenkins